National Women's Health Network records SSC.MS.00360
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IX. PROJECTS, PROGRAMS, AND REFORM EFFORTS, 1963-2007
  - Diethystilbestrol (DES) Project
    - DES: Self- assessment, 2003 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - DES Task force Report (NIH), 1978 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Legal issues and litigation
      - Articles and clippings, 1979-94 (Box 164, Folder 9)
      - DES Litigation Service (Box 164)
        [see Litigation Information Service]
      - Joyce Bichler v. Eli Lilly, 1979-81 (Box 164, Folder 10)
      - Payton et al. v. Abbott Labs, 1979 (Box 164, Folder 11)
      - Statements and testimonies before Congress, 1981 (Box 164, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-89 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Meetings, 1972-80 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - NWHN press releases and statements, 1980-83, n.d. (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Organizations
      - DES Action, 1977-95 (Box 165, Folder 3)
      - DES National Education Campaign Working Group (CDC), 2000 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Research, 1974-80 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Testimonies and transcripts, 1973-80 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-80, n.d. (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Endorsements
    - Henry Foster for Surgeon General, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984-2005 (Box 165, Folder 9-12)
  - Epilepsy Outreach Project, 1998 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Health Advocacy in Rural America
    [see Series V. MEMBERSHIP AND FINANCIAL MATERIALS -- Fundraising -- Grants -- Projects]
  - Informed consent
    - College Health Services Survey
      - Correspondence, 1983-85 (Box 166, Folder 3)
      - Information sheets on oral contraceptives and diaphragms, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 4)
      - Responses, 1983 (Box 166, Folder 5-6)
    - Correspondence, 1982-86 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Public Forum on Informed Consent (FDA-NIH), 1995 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - "Written Informed Consent and Long-acting Contraception: Disincentive to Coercion" (NWHN), 1998 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Insurance reform
    - Insurance Reform Working Group, 1986-87 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Medical malpractice insurance, 1985-2005 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - National health insurance plan, 1992 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Sex discrimination and health and disability insurance, 1983 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Lesbian Health
    - Lesbian Health Packet, 1982-92 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Taskforce: Lesbian Health Issues and Recommendations, 1993 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic, 1991, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Litigation Information Service
    - Correspondence
      - Requests for information
        - Benedictin, 1983-84 (Box 167, Folder 9)
        - Dalkon Shield, 1983-85 (Box 167, Folder 10)
        - Depo-Provera, 1983-85 (Box 167, Folder 11)
        - DES, 1975-85 (Box 167, Folder 12)
        - Medical records, 1982-83 (Box 167, Folder 13)
        - Tampax and toxic shock syndrome, 1981-84 (Box 168, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous, 1982-85 (Box 168, Folder 2-4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-88 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Forms, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Legal issues, 1985-86 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Procedures, 1986-87 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Mental Health
    - Electroconvulsive therapy, 1980-83 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Mental Health Project, 1982 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Premenstrual Syndrome and Premenstrual Dysphoric Disorder, 1985-86 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Midlife and Older Women Project
    - Budgets and project information, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Caregivers to the aged, 1981-85 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - House Select Committee on Aging, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - National Coalition on Older Women's Issues, 1984-85 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Nursing home reform
      - Citizens for the Improvement of Nursing Homes, 1983 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Georgia Nursing Home Legislation, 1981 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - National Citizens' Coalition for Nursing Home Reform, 1982-88 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Older Women's Health Committee
      [see SERIES III. COMMITTEES]
    - Older Women's League, 1982, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Pepper Commission, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Senate Subcommittee on Aging, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - The Older Woman: Continuities and Discontinuities, 1978 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1971, 1981 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - White House Mini Conference on Older Women, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Nursing education funding legislation, 1982-88 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Occupational health and safety: glutaraldehyde poisoning, 1995-97 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Pap tests, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Pregnancy and childbirth
    - Bendectin Registry, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Cesareans and episiotomies, 1980-95 (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - NWHN testimony
      - Bendectin, 1980-84 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Fetal monitoring, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Induction of labor, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Preterm labor, 1993 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Candidates, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Rights
    [see also Title X]
    - Abortion
      - Abortion choice and teens, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Abortion clinic protocol (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Abortion in the Era of States Rights, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Abortion Information Exchange meeting, 1982-83 (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Abortion Rights Action Week, 1979 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Abortion Speakout (Redstockings 20th anniversary), 1989 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Clinic violence (Hearings of the House Judiciary Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights)
        - Abortion Clinic Bombings and Fake Clinics 1986-87 (Box 171, Folder 8)
        - Clinic Violence, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 9)
      - Fake Clinic Project
        [See also Clinic violence]
        - Background information, 1985-86 (Box 171, Folder 10)
        - Brochures from fake clinics, 1984, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 11)
        - Expose "Fake Clinic" Campaign (PPFA), 1987 (Box 171, Folder 12)
        - Geraldo, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 13)
        - NWHN outreach materials and press listings, 1988, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 14)
        - Responses, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 15)
        - Yellow pages, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous, 1987-88, n.d. (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Federal funding of anti-abortion clinics, 1987 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Hatch Amendment, 1981-85 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - In Support of Women's Lives, 1982 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - March for Women's Lives, 1989, 2004 (Box 172, Folder 4-5)
      - Menstrual extraction, 1989-93 (Box 172, Folder 6)
      - Mobilize for Women's Lives, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Organizations
        - Abortion Action Coalition, 1977, n.d. (Box 173, Folder 1)
        - Abortion Fund, 1980 (Box 173, Folder 2)
        - Abortion Rights Mobilization, 1979-85 (Box 173, Folder 3)
        - Coalition for the Protection of Women's Health, 1984 (Box 173, Folder 4)
        - Ms. Foundation Reproductive Rights Coalition Fund, 1988-89 (Box 173, Folder 5)
        - National Abortion Rights Action League 1981-85 (Box 173, Folder 6)
        - National Campaign to Restore Abortion Funding, 1984-85 (Box 173, Folder 7)
        - National Organization for Women, 1979 (Box 173, Folder 8)
        - Pro-Choice Coalition, 1988-89 (Box 173, Folder 9)
        - Public Education Project, 2004 (Box 173, Folder 10)
        - Reproductive Rights National Network, 1985 (Box 173, Folder 11)
      - Press releases and position papers, 1978-85 (Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Roe v. Wade 10th and 13th Anniversary, 1983-86 (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - "Silent No More" Campaign, 1985 (Box 173, Folder 14)
      - "Silent Scream" (anti-abortion film), 1985 (Box 173, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1980-89, n.d. (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Campaign to Stop Anti-fertility Vaccines, 1996-2001 (Box 174)
      - 1993-95 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - 1996-2002 (Box 174, Folder 1A)
    - Contraception
      [see also Dalkon Shield, Depo-provera, and DES]
      - Contraceptive Research
        - Critiques, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 2)
        - Survey: Contraceptive Research Priorities (Judy Norsegian), 1978 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Emergency contraception
        - Historical look, 1980 (Box 174, Folder 4)
        - Morning after pill testimony, 1979-80 (Box 174, Folder 5-5A)
        - Miscellaneous, 1979-2005 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Lea's Shield, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Mecklenburg petition, 1983 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Norplant, 1985-93 (Box 175, Folder 1)
        [see also Depo-Provera Project]
      - Oral Contraception, 1980 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - C.R.A.C.K. Program (Children Requiring a Caring Community), 2000-01 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Sterilization abuse
    - Abstract, 1980 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1977-80 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Press release, 1978 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Survey of sterilization practices, 1983 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-95, n.d. (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Survey of Young Women, 2001 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Tampons and toxic shock syndrome
    - Absorbency and tampon labeling, 1981-87 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1979-83 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Federal Drug Administration, 1974-85 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Ingredients in tampons, 1979-81 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - NWHN press releases, information packet, and report, 1980-84, n.d. (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Tampons Task Force
      - 1981-82 (Box 177, Folder 3-7)
      - 1983-84 (Box 178, Folder 1-3)
    - Tampons and contraceptive sponges, 1980-83, n.d. (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - "Toxic Shock Syndrome & Tampons: Pilot Education Program Evaluation, 1984 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-80, n.d. (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Title X
    [see also Reproductive Rights]
    - Regulations, 1987-90 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - School based clinics, 1987 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Title X Coalition, 1985-87 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-88, n.d. (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Weight Discrimination Advocacy, 1999-2002 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - Women and AIDS Project
    - Advocacy project, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - AIDS education activity workshop, 1987 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - AIDS registry (ideas on), 1988 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Conferences
      - Women's Voices: Speaking AIDS, 1991-92 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-91 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Epidemiology of AIDS report, 1997 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Organizations (related)
      - Center for Disease Control, 1988-91 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - D.C. Committee on Women and AIDS, 1987 (Box 180, Folder 8)
      - Hispanic AIDS Committee, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - National Commission on AIDS, 1990, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - National Organizations Responding to AIDS, 1991-93 (Box 180, Folder 11)
      - National Resource Center on Women and AIDS, 1988-90 (Box 180, Folder 12)
      - New York Taskforce on Women and AIDS, 1991 (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - Women and AIDS Resource Center, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Publications, reports and statements
      [see also SERIES VI. PUBLICATIONS AND REPORTS]
      - Advice for life: A woman's guide to AIDS risks and prevention, by Chris Norwood: correspondence and marketing, 1987 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - AIDS: What every woman needs to know: correspondence and marketing, 1988 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous reports and statements, 1987-93 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Seminar on AIDS (ideas on), 1988 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Surveys
      - Hospital survey on AIDS transmission in pregnancy, 1988
        - Replies (Box 181, Folder 5)
        - Statistics (Box 181, Folder 6)
      - Survey on public policies related to women and AIDS: contact sheets, 1990-91 (Box 181, Folder 7-10)
      - State health departments, 1990-91
        - Alabama - Missouri (Box 182, Folder 1-26)
        - Montana -Tennessee (Box 183, Folder 1-19)
        - Texas - Wyoming (Box 184, Folder 1-9)
        - Report and guidelines, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous evaluation, notes, lists, and correspondence, 1990-97 (Box 184, Folder 11)
      - AIDS Network phone tree, 1990-91 (Box 184, Folder 12)
      - Prevention Survey, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-92, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 14)
  - Women and Smoking Project
    - Advertising, 1978,-85, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001-2003 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Women of Color
    [see also Black Women's Health Project]
    - "Chicanas as Healers" by Sandra Salazar, 1981 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Institute of Women and Ethnic Studies, 2000 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Native American Women and closure of inpatient services at the Indian Health Services Unit, Wagner, South Dakota, 1988-89 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Public hearing, 1985 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-2004, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Women's clinics
    - Clinic lists, 1985-98, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and printed material, 1989-2002, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Sandra Morgen clinic survey and report, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - Women's Health Vote, 1984-84 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Women's Vote Project
    - Description and consultant agreement, 1984, n.d. (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Voter registration notebook, 1984 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Voting records, 1983-84 (Box 186, Folder 4)
- SERIES X. COURT CASES AND LEGISLATION, 1977-2005
  This series contains court documents, subpoenas, depositions, correspondence, transcripts, printed materials, and testimonies. It is divided into two subseries: Court cases and Legislation. Court cases consists of three sections: Amicus briefs, NWHN as litigant, and Miscellaneous. Over the years the NWHN filed amicus briefs for many court cases. The first section contains court documents, transcripts and correspondence related to sixty court cases on a wide range of subjects including abortion, drugs during pregnancy, domestic violence, health insurance, and environmental and occupational hazards. They are arranged alphabetically by case name and topics for each case are noted. The Legislation section contains material related to six court cases in which the NWHN was one of the litigants. Of particular interest is NWHN v. A.H. Robins (Dalkon Shield) and NWHN v. Upjohn (Depo-Provera). Additional information on these two cases can be found in Series IX. PROJECTS, PROGRAMS, AND REFORM EFFORTS. The Miscellaneous section contains files on cases of interest collected by the Network including those where staff provided depositions. The second subseries contains files on various legislation of interest to the Network.
  - Court cases
    - Amicus Briefs
      - In re A.C. (forced cesarean), 1987-90 (Box 187, Folder 1-3)
      - Akron v. Akron (abortion), 1982 (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Alabama v. Tracy Padgett (drugs during pregnancy - fetal abuse), 1995 (Box 187, Folder 5)
      - Anonymous v. anonymous (incest), 1989 (Box 187, Folder 6)
      - Ashcroft v. Raich (medical marijuana), 2004 (Box 187, Folder 7)
      - Bost v. Low-income women of Texas (Medicaid funding for abortion), 2001 (Box 187, Folder 8)
      - Bowen v. Kendrick (abortion), 1987 (Box 187, Folder 9)
      - Bowen v. Massachusetts (Title X), 1988 (Box 187, Folder 10)
      - Bray v. Alexandria Women's Health Clinic (abortion), 1991 (Box 187, Folder 11)
      - Browning-Ferris v. Kelco Disposal (waste disposal), 1989 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Brzonkala v. Morrison, et. al (violence against women), 1999 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Califano v. Westcott (benefits), 1978 (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - California v. Green et. al. (battered women), 1994 (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Cassidy & Bell v. Smith (incest), 1989-92 (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Cipollone v. Liggett, Philip Morris, Lowe's Theatres (cigarettes), 1991 (Box 188, Folder 6)
      - Collins v. Texas (drug use during pregnancy), 1994 (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Kemp (drugs during pregnancy), 1993 (Box 188, Folder 8)
      - Dalrymple v. Brown (child sexual abuse), 1996 (Box 188, Folder 9)
      - Ferguson v. Charleston, S.C. (doctor/patient confidentiality), 1999-2000 (Box 188, Folder 10)
      - Grant v. General Motors (sex discrimination), 1989 (Box 188, Folder 11)
      - Guardianship of Sharon Kowalski (non-traditional families), 1991 (Box 188, Folder 12)
      - Grijalva v. Shalala (Medicare), 1997 (Box 188, Folder 13)
      - Harris v. McRae (abortion), 1979-80 (Box 188, Folder 14)
      - Hartigan v. Zbaraz (abortion), 1986 (Box 188, Folder 15)
      - Henley v. FD (oral contraceptives and breast cancer), 1995 (Box 188, Folder 16)
      - Hill v. Colorado (abortion), 1999 (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Hodgson v. Minnesota (parental consent), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 2)
      - Illinois v. Madison (HIV testing), 1990 (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Jane Doe v. John Smith (abortion), 1988 (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - Johnson v. Florida (drugs during pregnancy - delivering drugs to a minor), 1990-92 (Box 189, Folder 5)
      - Kane et. al. v. Johns Manville (exposure to asbestos), 1987 (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Katz v. Ohio Board of Psychology (licensing of psychologists), 1981 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Lavetter v. International Playtex (toxic shock), 1988 (Box 189, Folder 8)
      - Leigh v. Board of Registry in Nursing (midwifery), 1986 (Box 189, Folder 9)
      - Lohr v. Medtronic (medical device - pacemaker), 1996 (Box 189, Folder 10)
      - Moe v. Hanley (abortion), n.d. (Box 190, Folder 1)
      - Nash v. NYC Trust (pregnancy discrimination ), 1991 (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - National Educators Association of Rhode Island et. al. v. Garrahy et. al. (coverage of abortions), 1985 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - New Jersey v. Smith (HIV), 1991 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - New Mexico v. Cynthia Martinez (drugs during pregnancy), 2007 (Box 190, Folder 5)
      - New York State Society of Surgeons v. Axelrod (HIV testing), 1991 (Box 190, Folder 6)
      - New York v. Bowen (Title X), 1988 (Box 190, Folder 7)
      - Norris and Turensky v. Nelson (incarcerated women and childbirth), n.d. (Box 190, Folder 8)
      - Northeast Women's Center v. McMonagle et. al. (abortion), 1989 (Box 190, Folder 9)
      - People v. Jones, (drugs during pregnancy - fetal abuse), 1993 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - Planned Parenthood of Southeastern Pennsylvania v. Casey (abortion), 1992 (Box 190, Folder 11)
      - PPFA v. Bowen (abortion), 1988 (Box 190, Folder 12)
      - Richardson v. Merrill-Dow Pharmaceutical (Bendectin), 1989 (Box 190, Folder 13)
      - Roberts v. Galen (uninsured patients), 1998 (Box 190, Folder 14)
      - Silkwood v. Kerr-McGee (nuclear hazard), 1983 (Box 190, Folder 15)
      - State v. Carter (drugs during pregnancy -fetal abuse), 1991 (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - Thomson v. OSU Hospital (family and medical leave), 1998 (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - Thornburgh v. ACOG (abortion), 1985 (Box 191, Folder 3)
      - UAW v. Johnson Controls (occupational lead exposure), 1989-91 (Box 191, Folder 4)
      - Washington (state) v. Dunn (drugs during pregnancy- fetal abuse), 1995-96 (Box 191, Folder 5)
      - Washington (state) v. Glucksberg (protection of the terminally ill), 1996 (Box 191, Folder 6)
      - Webster v. Reproductive Health Systems (abortion), 1989 (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - Whitner v. South Carolina (drugs during pregnancy), 1998 (Box 191, Folder 8)
      - Wisconsin (state) v. Kruziicki et al (drugs during pregnancy - fetal abuse), 1996 (Box 191, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989-97 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - NWHN as litigant
      [see also SERIES IX. PROJECTS, PROGRAMS, AND REFORM EFFORTS]
      - ARM (Abortion Rights Mobilization) v. Regan and ARM v. Brady, 1981-90 (Box 191, Folder 11)
      - Matria v. National Women's Health Network and John Does 1-10 (deceptive trade practices), 1997 (Box 191, Folder 12)
      - National Women's Health Network v. A.H. Robins (Dalkon Shield), 1981 (Box 191, Folder 13)
      - National Women's Health Network v. Upjohn (Depo-Provera), 1985-88 (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Public Citizen Health Group and National Women's Health Network v. FDA (banning drug Parlodel), 1994 (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Public Citizen, National Women's Health Network et al v. Department of Health and Human Services (patient package inserts), 1977-82 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Erickson v. CPC, Inc. (sex discrimination), 1980-81 (Box 192, Folder 6)
      - Health Research Group v. Department of HEW (federally funded medical services), 1979 (Box 192, Folder 7)
      - NOW v. Mutual of Omaha (pregnancy insurance discrimination),1984 (Box 192, Folder 8)
      - Ormai v. Searle, 1990 (Box 193, Folder 9)
      - Pathfinder Fund v. USAID (abortion research), 1990 (Box 193, Folder 1)
      - Shannon v. Fresno County, 1989 (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - Thompson and Lee et. al. v. Proctor & Gamble (TSS), 1980 (Box 193, Folder 3)
      - Turnock v. Ragsdale (abortion), 1989 (Box 193, Folder 4)
      - Watson v. Eli Lilly (DES), 1983 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Legislation
    - Act for Better Child Care Services (SB 2046), 1986-88 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Adolescent Family Life Act, 1985 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Federal Policy Act, 1988 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Alternative Breast Cancer Treatments Information for Patients Act, 1987 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Baby Doe legislation, 1983-85 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Catastrophic Health Insurance: Medigap and Spousal Impoverishment, 1987 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Civil Rights Restoration Act, 1987 (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Fairness in Insurance (HR 2727), 1988 (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - FCC Fairness Doctrine, 1981 (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Health maintenance organizations (HR 2480 and HR 2508), 1981 (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - High Risk Occupational Disease Notification and Prevention Act, 1988 (Box 193, Folder 16)
    - Human Genome legislation, 1988 (Box 193, Folder 17)
    - Kennedy/Waxman Minimum Essential Health Benefits for All Workers Act, (S 1265, HR 2506), 1987 (Box 193, Folder 18)
    - Long Term Care Insurance, 1978-89, n.d. (Box 193, Folder 19)
    - Medicare Coverage for Mammography Examinations, 1987-88 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - New York Maternal Information Act, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Parental Leave Bill (HR 925), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Reproductive Health Equity Act, 1984-85 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Smoking Bills (S 1937), 1985 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Surrogacy Arrangements Act (HR 2433), 1988 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Warning Labels on Alcoholic Beverages (S2047), 1988 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Welfare Reform Bill (Kennedy), 1987 (Box 194, Folder 8)
- SERIES XI. OUTREACH AND PUBLIC RELATIONS, 1977-2005